(Sheldon(on phone):)This is Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
(Sheldon(on phone):)Yeah, I need to cancel my membership
to the planetarium.
[LAUGHING NOISELESSLY]
(Sheldon(on phone):)Yeah, well, I'm sorry too...
(Sheldon(on phone):)...but there's just no room
for you in my wallet.
No, I understand, but it was between
you and the Museum of Natural History...
(Sheldon(on phone):)...and frankly, you don't have dinosaurs.
Oh, I'll miss you too. Bye-bye.
(Sheldon(on phone):)Okay, I know you're texting about me
and I'd really like you to stop.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
(Raj(entering):)Oh, dear, I am rightly and truly screwed.
(Leonard:)I thought you were finding new friends.
(Raj:)I've got some feelers out.
(Raj:)In the meantime, listen to this.
[ON RECORDING]
Hi, Rajesh, this is Lalita Gupta.
(Lalita(voice from Raj's phone):)Your mother gave my mother
your phone number to give to me.
So I'm calling you and call me back.
(Raj:)Bye.
(Raj:)Can you believe how pushy she is?